{
    "questions": [
        {
            "number": 1,
            "question": "Javascript is an _______ language?",
            "answers": [
                "Object-oriented",
                "Object-based",
                "Procedural",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 1
        },
        {
            "number": 2,
            "question": "Which of the following keywords is not used to define a variable in Javascript?",
            "answers": [
                "let",
                "===",
                "const",
                "var"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "number": 3,
            "question": "Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript?",
            "answers": [
                "getElementById()",
                "getElementByClassName()",
                "Both A and B",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 3
        },
        {
            "number": 4,
            "question": "Upon encountering empty statements, what does the Javascript Interpreter do?",
            "answers": [
                "Throws an error",
                "Ignores the statements",
                "Gives a warning",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "number": 5,
            "question": "Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
            "answers": [
                "document.write()",
                "console.log()",
                "window.alert()",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 4
        },
        {
            "number": 6,
            "question": "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
            "answers": [
                "const",
                "let",
                "var",
                "constant"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 1
        },
        {
            "number": 7,
            "question": "What keyword is used to check whether a given property is valid or not?",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "isIn",
                "exists",
                "lies"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 1
        },
        {
            "number": 8,
            "question": "What is the use of the 'noscript' tag in Javascript?",
            "answers": [
                "The contents are displayed by non-JS-based browsers.",
                "Clears all the cookies and cache.",
                "Allows you to comment inside the tags.",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 1
        },
        {
            "number": 9,
            "question": "When an operator's value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is:",
            "answers": [
                "Boolean",
                "undefined",
                "object",
                "integer"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 3
        },
        {
            "number": 10,
            "question": "What does the Javascript 'debugger' statement do?",
            "answers": [
                "It will debug all the errors in the program at runtime.",
                "It acts as a breakpoint in the program.",
                "It will debug error in the current statement if any.",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 2
        }
    ]
}